# Justin Wasser

# Baltimore, MD (301) 801-2210 | justinwasser1@gmail.com

# **Summary**

I am pursuing an information security analyst role having completed a master's degree in information assurance and acquired a Security+ certification. I currently work as a technology generalist for a law firm and previously worked as a headhunter in a sole proprietorship.

#### **Skills**

- Python
- SQL
- Linux line-command
- SIEM (Splunk, Chronicle)
- NIST Frameworks CSF & RMF
- Wireshark

- Nessus
- SEO
- Web Development
- Google Ads
- Google Analytics
- PowerPoint

### **Experience**

Law Office of David Wasser- Technology Generalist/Paralegal

06 / 2021 – Present

- Redesigned the company website, resulting in significantly improved website health and SEO scores, with no prior website development or SEO experience.
  - ➤ Website redesign led to an ~80% increase in average engagement time for users, and a significant reduction in bounce rate.
  - ➤ Website health score was ~60 (according to ahrefs) before the update and is currently 95.
  - Improvements resulted from optimizing the site for mobile device browsing and fixing issues with the site architecture (broken links, unindexed web pages, sitemap gaps, URL issues, etc.)
  - ➤ Website link: <u>wasserlawmd.com</u>
- Developed and managed Ad Hoc Google Ad Campaigns that outperformed previous campaigns created by an SME according to all relevant metrics i.e., Cost-per-click (CPC), Conversion rate, and Cost per conversion.
- Deploy and troubleshoot office devices including desktops, mobile devices, and printers.
- Produce PowerPoint slides for use during jury trials.
- Craft various legal documents as needed (motions, requests for records, etc.).

- Delivered qualified candidates for IT positions requiring security clearances for government contractors.
  - ➤ Positions include Journeyman Computer Programmers, Sr. Computer Programmers, Sr. Network and Computer Systems Administrators, Sr. Computer Network Architects, and an SME Database Administrator.
- Provided qualified candidates for the financial services industry with a focus on commercial real estate and multifamily at all levels including underwriting, asset management, servicing, closing, and affordable housing roles.
  - ➤ Clients included one of the largest multifamily lenders in the United States.
  - ➤ The highest level placed was a Consents Asset Manager.
- Took on difficult searches that other firms could not fill and delivered quality candidates for various other professional roles using critical thinking to locate non-obvious talent.
- Achieved favorable contingency search agreement terms between Point Break Staffing and numerous clients.

## The Hire Authority- Contract Recruiter

09 / 2013 - 12 / 2016

• Located candidates utilizing LinkedIn and Craigslist, screened them, and if qualified submitted them for consideration for various client openings.

#### **Education**

#### **Towson University**

Bachelor of Science- BS, Philosophy

UMGC (2022-2024)

MS IT- Information Assurance 4.0 GPA

#### **Certifications**

CompTIA Security+

#### **Certificates**

Google Cybersecurity Certificate